Guide to the William T. Grant Foundation records FA004
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant files, 1940-1990s, bulk 1970-1985; 1970-1985; 3; Tavistock Institute of Human Relations; Spock, Benjamin (1903-1998); Freud, Anna (1895-1982); Hampstead Child-Therapy Clinic; Goodall, Jane (1934); 96.9 Cubic Feet 246 letter document boxes, 5 legal document boxes, 4 half-legal boxes, 1 card f
  - Grant files, 1946-1990s, bulk 1970s; 1970-1979; C
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #8 - Dieta E. Accresciemento - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D.; Galeotti Flori (72-0097-56), 1957 (Box 239, Folder 3387)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #9 - Eurpoean Research in Child Psychology - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D.; Galeotti Flori (72-0097-56), 1958 (Box 239, Folder 3388)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #10 - Metodo Per La Misurazione dell' Efficienza Intellettiva - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1958 (Box 239, Folder 3389)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #11 - Esplorazione dei Motivi - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1961 (Box 239, Folder 3390)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #12 - Esplorazione dei Motivi - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D.; P.H. Mussen; P. Urbano (72-0097-56), 1961 (Box 239, Folder 3391)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #13 - Selezione Dopo La Quinta Elementare Nella Scuole Italiane - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D.; G. Tesi (72-0097-56), 1961 (Box 239, Folder 3392)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #14 - Detection and Encouragement of the Talented in Italian Schools - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1962 (Box 239, Folder 3393)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #15 - Estimation of Social Class - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1962 (Box 239, Folder 3394)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #16 - Influence of Town and County Upon Children's Intelligence - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D., et. al. (72-0097-56), 1962 (Box 239, Folder 3395)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #17 - A Standardization of Raven's Progressive Matrices - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1962 (Box 239, Folder 3396)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #18 - A Study of Dental Health in American Children of Italian Origin - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1962 (Box 239, Folder 3397)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #19 - The Influence of Father-Son Relationships - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D., et. al. (72-0097-56), 1963 (Box 239, Folder 3398)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #20 - Events of Puberty in III Florentine Girls - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D., et. al. (72-0097-56), 1964 (Box 239, Folder 3399)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #21 - Aging and Adolescence - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D., et. al. (72-0097-56), 1963 (Box 239, Folder 3400)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #22 - Deprivation of Maternal Care - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D., et. al. (72-0097-56), 1963 (Box 239, Folder 3401)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #23 - Fatigue and Growth - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1962-1963 (Box 239, Folder 3402)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #24 - Body Composition, Culture, and Sex - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1965 (Box 239, Folder 3403)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #25 - Blood Groups and Personality Traits - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1964 (Box 239, Folder 3404)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #26 - Growth and Environment - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1965 (Box 239, Folder 3405)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #27 - Interim Report on a Study of Achievement Orientation - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1964 (Box 239, Folder 3406)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #28 - Personality Characteristics of Converted Left Handers - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1966 (Box 240, Folder 3407)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #29 - Some Somatic and Psychological Observations - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1966 (Box 240, Folder 3408)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #30 - Evaluation of Physical Maturity at Adolescence - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1968 (Box 240, Folder 3409)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #31 - Special Needs of Adolescents - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1968 (Box 240, Folder 3410)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #32 - A Longitudinal Study on Adolescence - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D. (72-0097-56), 1968 (Box 240, Folder 3411)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #33 - Two Cities and their Effect Upon Rural Immigrants - Harban Boutourline-Young, M.D.; Frank Barron, Ph.D. (72-0097-56), 1968 (Box 240, Folder 3412)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Harvard #34 - Long Term Effects of Environment Upon Growth and Health - Harban Boutourline-Young (72-0097-56), 1961 (Box 240, Folder 3413)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Yale #1 - Adolescence - Harban Boutourline-Young (72-0097-56), undated (Box 240, Folder 3414)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Yale #2 - Socio-economic Factors in Child Development - Harban Boutourline-Young (72-0097-56), 1970 (Box 240, Folder 3415)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Yale #3 - Perceived Opportunity, Alienation, and Drinking Behavior - Harban Boutourline-Young (72-0097-56), 1970 (Box 240, Folder 3416)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Yale #4 - Rome and Boston - Harban Boutourline-Young; Frank Barron (72-0097-56), 1970 (Box 240, Folder 3417)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Yale #6 - Genetics and Environment as Factors in Child Development - Harban Boutourline-Young (72-0097-56), 1972 (Box 240, Folder 3418)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Yale #7 - Emergence of Deciduous Teeth in Tunisian Children... - Harban Boutourline-Young; R. Saracci, M. Bamabach (72-0097-56), 1973 (Box 240, Folder 3419)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Yale #8 - Emergence of Deciduous Teeth in Tunisian Children... - Harban Boutourline-Young; R. Saracci, M. Bamabach (72-0097-56), 1973 (Box 240, Folder 3420)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publication, Yale #9 - Social and Environmental Factors Accompanying Malnutrition - Harban Boutourline-Young (72-0097-56), 1973 (Box 240, Folder 3421)
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publications - CIBA Foundation Lecture: "Adolescence and Aging," Slides - Harban Boutourline-Young (72-0097-56), 19 October 1962 (Box 240, Folder 3422)
      See Series 5a, Special Formats (Scrapbooks and Photographs), box 283, folder 3583.
    - Harvard / Yale Florence Research Project - Publications - Annual Report (W.T. Grant) - Harban Boutourline-Young (72-0097-56), 1969 (Box 240, Folder 3423)
    - Harvard University - Child Development in Rural Kenya - Jerome Kagan; Charles Super, 1973-1977 (Box 240, Folder 3424-3425)
    - Harvard University - Infancy in Rural Africa - Jerome Kagan; Charles Super, 1972-1973 (Box 241, Folder 3426)
    - Harvard University - Graduate School of Education - Film: "Black Psychiatrists" - Chester Pierce, 1971-1976 (Box 241, Folder 3427)
    - Harvard University, Harvard Medical School - Hormone Metabolism in the Brain - Kenneth T. Ryan, M.D. (72-0466-72), 1971-1975 (Box 241, Folder 3428)
    - Harvard University, Harvard Medical School - Hormone Metabolism in the Brain - Kenneth T. Ryan, M.D. (72-0466-72), 1975 (Box 241, Folder 3429)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Malnutrition and Psychological Development - M. Guillermo Herrera, M.D., 1973-1974 (Box 241, Folder 3430)
    - Hospital Audiences, Inc. - Michael Jon Spencer, 1974-1979 (Box 241, Folder 3431)
      See Series 5c, Special Formats (Audiovisual and digital material), reel 14.
    - Hospital Audiences, Inc. - Michael Jon Spencer, 1970-1971 (Box 241, Folder 3432)
    - University of Hawaii - David H. Crowell, 1972-1981 (Box 241, Folder 3433)
    - University of Hawaii - John McDermott; Thomas W. Maretzki, 1979 (Box 241, Folder 3434)
    - University of Illinois - Finance - Ernest A. Haggard, Ph.D., 1971-1975 (Box 241, Folder 3435)
    - University of Illinois - Publication - Ernest A. Haggard, 1978 (Box 241, Folder 3436)
    - University of Illinois - Donald R. Peterson; Steven L. Golding, 1975-1983 (Box 241, Folder 3437)
    - University of Illinois - Administration - Arnold J. Samroff, 1974-1979 (Box 241, Folder 3438)
    - University of Illinois - Reports, Finance - Arnold J. Samroff, 1979-1981 (Box 241, Folder 3439)
    - University of Illinois - Philip Teitelbaum, 1974-1978 (Box 241, Folder 3440)
    - University of Illinois, The Board of Trustees - Donald White, 1972-1979 (Box 241, Folder 3441)
    - Indiana University, History Institute for Sex Research - Paul H. Gebhard, 1971-1979 (Box 241, Folder 3442)
    - Institute for Behavioral Research - Edgar H. Brenner; Harold L. Cohen, 1975-1976 (Box 242, Folder 3443)
    - Institute for Behavioral Research - Edward Taub, 1974 (Box 242, Folder 3444)
    - Institute for Behavioral Research - Epp A. Miller, 1972-1974 (Box 242, Folder 3445)
    - Institute for Child Mental Health - David Shapiro, 1976-1977 (Box 242, Folder 3446)
      See Series 5c, Special Formats (Audiovisual and digital material), reels 9-11.
    - Institute for Child Mental Health - Herschel Alt, 1975-1976 (Box 242, Folder 3447)
    - Institute for Child Mental Health - Joseph and Jeanette Stone, 1973-1976 (Box 242, Folder 3448)
      See Series 5c, Special Formats (Audiovisual and digital material), reels xxx-xxx [3 Kibbutz films].
    - Institut National de la Sante et de la Recherche Medicale - Henry Hecaen (73-0470-73), 1973-1978 (Box 242, Folder 3449)
    - Institut National de la Sante et de la Recherche Medicale - Michell Schiff (73-0469-73) (82-0469-73), 1975-1981 (Box 242, Folder 3450)
    - Institut National de la Sante et de la Recherche Medicale - Michell Schiff (73-0469-73) (82-0469-73), 1978-1985 (Box 242, Folder 3451)
    - Institute of Psychiatry - George Ettlinger, 1974-1977 (Box 242, Folder 3452)
    - Institute for Research into Medical and Multiple Handicap - Peter Woodford, 1973-1976 (Box 242, Folder 3453)
    - International Society for the Study of Behavioral Development - Jan de Wit, 1976-1979 (Box 242, Folder 3454)
    - International Association for Child Psychiatry and Allied Professions - Albert Solnit, 1977-1980 (Box 242, Folder 3455)
    - Interseminarian Incorporated - Peter R. Sherer, 1970-1972 (Box 242, Folder 3456)
    - Jesse Lee Home - Richard Gilbert, 1970-1972 (Box 243, Folder 3457)
    - Jewish Board of Guardians - William Goldfarb, 1974-1978 (Box 243, Folder 3458)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Familial Factors - Barton Childs, 1979-1981 (Box 243, Folder 3459)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Terminal Support for M.D., Ph.D. Program - Joel Elkes, M.D., 1973-1976 (Box 243, Folder 3460)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Publications - Doris Entwisle (-0796-), 1987-1994 (Box 243, Folder 3461-3462)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Administration - John Money, Ph.D. (83-0869-00), 1983-1987 (Box 243, Folder 3463)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Application - John Money, Ph.D. (83-0869-00), 1982-1983 (Box 243, Folder 3464)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Finance - John Money, Ph.D. (83-0869-00), 1983-1987 (Box 243, Folder 3465)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Finance - John Money, Ph.D. (83-0869-00), 1983-1987 (Box 243, Folder 3466)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Reports / Publications - John Money, Ph.D. (83-0869-00), 1985-1988 (Box 243, Folder 3467)
    - Johns Hopkins University - John Money, Ph.D. (83-0869-00), 1983 (Box 243, Folder 3468)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Training Programs (-0113-), 1958-1959 (Box 243, Folder 3469)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Training Programs (-0113-), 1960-1963 (Box 244, Folder 3470)
    - Joint Commission on Accrediation of Hospitals - John Portersfield, 1977-1979 (Box 244, Folder 3471)
    - University of Kansas, Endowment Association - Medication, Labor, and Delivery, 1973-1975 (Box 244, Folder 3472)
    - University of Kansas, Medical Center - Michael Mieghan, 1977-1987 (Box 244, Folder 3473)
    - University of Kentucky - Roy Jarecky, 1975-1978 (Box 244, Folder 3474)
    - Layfayette Clinic - Thomas McNeil, 1972-1973 (Box 244, Folder 3475)
    - Legal Aid Bureau - Joseph Matera, 1973-1977 (Box 244, Folder 3476)
    - Legal Aid Society of New York - Archibald Murray, 1976-1977 (Box 244, Folder 3477)
    - University of London - Institute of Education - Basil Bernstein, 1973-1976 (Box 244, Folder 3478)
    - The Long Island College Hospital - Administration - Paula Krenkel, 1973-1981 (Box 244, Folder 3479)
      Photographs have been moved to Series 5a, Special Formats (Scrapbooks and Photographs), box 283, folder 3585.
    - The Long Island College Hospital - Report - Paula Krenkel, 1977 (Box 244, Folder 3480)
    - University of Louisville - Ronald Wilson, 1972-1975 (Box 244, Folder 3481)
    - Manhattan Country School - Augustus Trowbridge, 1973-1975 (Box 244, Folder 3482)
    - University of Marlyand, Child Study Center - Gerthon Morgan, 1970-1973 (Box 244, Folder 3483)
    - University of Marlyand, School of Medicine - Stanford Freedman; S. Michael Plant, 1974-1975 (Box 244, Folder 3484)
    - University of Marlyand, Child Study Center - Richard Louttit, Ph.D., 1973-1978 (Box 244, Folder 3485)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Loy D. Lytle, Ph.D.; John D. Fernstrom, Ph.D. - Protein Malnutrition, 1974-1976 (Box 244, Folder 3486)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Ernesto Pollitt - Ecology of Malnutrition, 1973-1977 (Box 244, Folder 3487)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Frances Schmitt; Frederic Worden - Neuroscience Research Program, 1972-1977 (Box 244, Folder 3488)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Frances Schmitt; Frederic Worden - Neuroscience Research Program, 1972-1977 (Box 244, Folder 3489)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Nervin Scrimshaw - Animal Studies in Malnutrition, 1974-1976 (Box 245, Folder 3490)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Hans-Lukas Teuber - Central Nervous System, 1971-1975 (Box 245, Folder 3491)
    - Massachusetts Mental Health Research Corporation - Henry Grunebaum, 1973-1976 (Box 245, Folder 3492)
    - McGill University - H.B.M. Murray, 1965-1968 (Box 245, Folder 3493)
    - McLean Hospital - Victor Shashoua, 1970-1975 (Box 245, Folder 3494)
    - The Medical and Health Research Association of New York City - June Christmas, 1975-1978 (Box 245, Folder 3495)
    - Meharry Medical College - Lloyd Elam, 1969-1975 (Box 245, Folder 3496)
    - Mental Health Film Board, Inc. - Alberta Jacoby, 1971-1973 (Box 245, Folder 3497)
      See Series 5c, Special Formats (Audiovisual and digital material), reel 27.
    - Mental Health Materials Center, Inc. - Rachel Cox, 1969-1982 (Box 245, Folder 3498)
    - The Merrill-Palmer Institute - Greta Fein; Patricia Voydanoff, 1977 (Box 245, Folder 3499)
    - Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund - Vilma Martinez, 1975-1977 (Box 245, Folder 3500)
    - University of Michigan - Selma Frailberg, 1978-1982 (Box 245, Folder 3501)
    - University of Michigan - Martin Gold, 1973-1976 (Box 245, Folder 3502)
    - University of Michigan - Lloyd Johnston; Jerome Johnston; Jerald Bachman, 1971-1973 (Box 245, Folder 3503)
    - University of Michigan - Gary Olson, 1975-1977 (Box 245, Folder 3504)
    - University of Michigan - Harold W. Stevenson, 1973-1979 (Box 245, Folder 3505-3507)
    - Millsaps College - Eugene Cain; Peter Stewart, 1976-1977 (Box 245, Folder 3508)
    - University of Minnesota - John Chambers; Herbert Pick, 1978 (Box 245, Folder 3509)
    - University of Minnesota - Williams Charlesworth, 1973-1974 (Box 245, Folder 3510)
    - University of Minnesota - Byron Egeland, 1988 (Box 245, Folder 3511)
    - University of Minnesota - Applications, Reports - Norman Garmezy (83-0702-78), 1979-1989 (Box 246, Folder 3268)
    - University of Minnesota - Administration - Norman Garmezy (83-0702-78), 1979-1990 (Box 246, Folder 3269)
    - University of Minnesota - Finance - Norman Garmezy (83-0702-78), 1983-1990 (Box 246, Folder 3270)
    - University of Minnesota - James Jenkins, 1972-1973 (Box 246, Folder 3271)
    - University of Minnesota - Philip Salapatek, 1972-1974 (Box 246, Folder 3272)
    - University of Minnesota - Sandra Scarr-Salapatek, 1972-1976 (Box 246, Folder 3273-3274)
    - University of Minnesota - Gerald Siegel; Herbert Pick, Jr., 1973-1976 (Box 246, Folder 3276)
    - University of Missouri, Columbia - Donald J. Farish, 1978-1979 (Box 246, Folder 3277)
    - Montefiore Hospital and Medical Center - Sigurd Ackerman, 1973-1976 (Box 246, Folder 3278)
    - Montefiore Hospital and Medical Center - Martin Cherasky, 1970-1974 (Box 246, Folder 3279)
    - Montefiore Hospital and Medical Center - Carter Marshall, 1974 (Box 246, Folder 3280)
    - Mount Sinai School of Medicine - Anne G. Morris, 1970-1977 (Box 246, Folder 3281-3282)
    - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund - Jack Greenburg, 1975-1978 (Box 246, Folder 3283)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Donald Ferderickson, 1974-1977 (Box 246, Folder 3284)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Leonard Laster, 1974 (Box 246, Folder 3285)
    - National Association for the Education of Young Children - Milton E. Akers, 1972-1974 (Box 246, Folder 3286)
    - National Association for Gifted Children - Henry Collins, 1975-1976 (Box 246, Folder 3287)
    - National Association for Mental Health - Mildred Bateman, 1973-1974 (Box 247, Folder 3288)
    - National Assembly of National Voluntary Health and Social Welfare Organizations - Hobart Burch, 1975-1979 (Box 247, Folder 3289)
    - National Association for the Prevention of Addiction to Narcotics - Harold Alksne, 1974-1976 (Box 247, Folder 3290)
    - National Board of Medical Examiners - Bryce Templeton, 1974-1977 (Box 247, Folder 3291)
    - National Board of the Young Women's Christian Association of the U.S.A. - Mary Gay Harm, 1979 (Box 247, Folder 3292)
    - National Committee for Citizens in Education - Carl Marburger, 1975-1976 (Box 247, Folder 3293)
    - National Committee for Citizens in Education - Dorothy Height, 1979-1981 (Box 247, Folder 3294)
    - National Council of Negro Women - Dorothy Height, 1972-1975 (Box 247, Folder 3295)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities - Arnold Nash, 1971 (Box 247, Folder 3296)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities - Meredith Wilson, 1970-1972 (Box 247, Folder 3297)
    - National Genetics Foundation - Henry Epstein, 1972-1975 (Box 247, Folder 3298)
    - National Information Bureau - M.C. Van de Workeen, 1975-1979 (Box 247, Folder 3299)
    - National Institute on the Gifted and Talented - David M. Jackson, 1976-1977 (Box 247, Folder 3300)
      The film "Who are these People" may pertain to the National Institute on the Gifted and Talented grant file. See Series 5c, Special Formats (Audiovisual and digital material), reel 13.
    - National Medical Fellowships - Robert C. Stepto, 1970-1971 (Box 247, Folder 3301)
    - University of Nevada - Allen and Beatrice Gardner, 1972-1978 (Box 247, Folder 3302)
    - The New York Academy of Sciences - Doris Aaronson; Robert Rieber, 1974-1975 (Box 247, Folder 3303)
    - The New York Academy of Sciences - Leonore Loeb Adler, 1975-1977 (Box 247, Folder 3304)
    - The New York Academy of Sciences - Horst D. Steklis, Ph.D.; Steven Harnad; Jane Beckman Lancaster, Ph.d., 1975-1976 (Box 247, Folder 3305)
    - New York Hospital, Cornell Medical Center - Elaine Heffner; Elizabeth Balliett, 1973 (Box 247, Folder 3306)
    - New York Medical College - Richard Brotman, 1974-1977 (Box 247, Folder 3307)
    - New York State Citizens' Council for Children, Youth, and their Families - Eleanor Kirk, 1979-1980 (Box 247, Folder 3308)
    - New York State Citizens' Council for Children, Youth, and their Families - Eleanor Kirk, 1979 (Box 248, Folder 3309)
    - New York University, Graduate School of Arts & Sciences - Robert Holt, 1974-1977 (Box 248, Folder 3310)
    - New York University Medical Center - Clark Randt, 1972-1979 (Box 248, Folder 3311)
    - New York University, Research Center for Mental Health - Hartvig Dahl, M.D.; Merton Gill, M.D., 1970-1974 (Box 248, Folder 3312)
    - New York University, Research Center for Mental Health - Robert Holt, 1973-1974 (Box 248, Folder 3313)
    - New York University, School of Law - Richard Hirsch, 1971-1975 (Box 248, Folder 3314)
    - New York University, School of Medicine - David Quartermain; Lewis Friedman, 1976 (Box 248, Folder 3315)
    - New York Urban Coalition - Administration - Louis McCagg, 1971-1972 (Box 248, Folder 3316)
    - New York Urban Coalition - Report - Louis McCagg, 1972 (Box 248, Folder 3317-3318)
    - New York Urban Coalition - Administration, Reports - Louis McCragg, 1975-1979 (Box 248, Folder 3319)
    - New York Urban Coalition - Final Report - Louis McCragg, 1979 (Box 248, Folder 3320)
    - New York Urban Coalition - Final Report - Louis McCragg, 1979 (Box 249, Folder 3321)
    - University of North Carolina, School of Medicine - Hector Farias, Jr., 1973-1975 (Box 249, Folder 3322-3323)
    - University of North Carolina, School of Public Health - Earl S. Schaefer, 1977-1979 (Box 249, Folder 3324)
    - Northeastern University - Harlan Lane, 1976-1986 (Box 249, Folder 3325)
      Photographs have been moved to Series 5a, Special Formats (Scrapbooks and Photographs), box 283, folder 3586.
    - Nursing Scholarship Foundation - Dale Woodcock, 1972-1973 (Box 249, Folder 3326)
    - Offender Aid and Restoration of the U.S. - Jay Worrell, 1975-1977 (Box 249, Folder 3327)
    - Offender Aid and Restoration of the U.S. - Jay Worrell, 1977-1978 (Box 250, Folder 3328)
    - Ohio State University Foundation - Samuel Corson, 1974-1979 (Box 250, Folder 3329)
    - Oregon Research Institute - Lita Furby, 1974-1978 (Box 250, Folder 3330)
    - Oregon Research Foundation - Final Report - Lita Furby, 1976 (Box 250, Folder 3331)
    - The Orton Society - Roger Saunders, 1974-1975 (Box 250, Folder 3332)
    - Pacific Oaks College - Administration - Georgiana Feeney, 1975-1979 (Box 250, Folder 3333)
    - Pacific Oaks College - Progress Report - Georgiana Feeney, 1974 (Box 250, Folder 3334-3335)
      Photographs have been moved to Series 5a, Special Formats (Scrapbooks and Photographs), box 283, folder 3587.
    - Pacific Oaks College - Program Report, 1978 (Box 250, Folder 3336-3337)
    - Pacific Oaks College - Program Report, Part I, 1975-1976 (Box 250, Folder 3338)
      Photographs have been moved to Series 5a, Special Formats (Scrapbooks and Photographs), box 283, folder 3588.
    - Pacific Oaks College - Program Report, Parts I and II, 1975-1976 (Box 251, Folder 3339-3341)
    - Palace of Arts and Sciences Foundation - Frank Oppenheimer (77-0640-77), 1977-1979 (Box 251, Folder 3342)